Listen, I get it. A lot of y'all are used to people who really don't stand on nothing, you know, like people who switch up for the bad, quote unquote.
I know a lot of y'all are used to people who consider politics to be just an accepted system of capitulation and lies. And that is something that people are very accustomed to.
And so when you meet someone like myself, you are befuddled, confused, annoyed, irritated at the rigidity of my stance on things.
And the things that I have a rigidity on are that which I have studied and understand and know.
And so as I have grown and evolved as a person, I understand that in the past, I used to have a stubbornness that was rooted in ego and that was also aligned with a very groupthink mindset.
However, in my growth, in my evolution, I have removed that ego to be open for knowledge, not open for manipulation, not open for capitulation and not open to mitigate feelings.
No, I am open for information that is going to evolve. And the beauty of being in that practice on such a regular basis is that you are able to then identify when information is advancing you and evolving you or when it is manipulating you.
So when people are upset about realities around candidates, I find it very unfortunate for them, right?
Because I'm not going to move and shake on that which I know to be the case.
And I know that Zionism is at the root and is a fundamental factor of where, of why colonialism and imperialism continues to displace people from their homes to destroy and disrupt the sovereignty of particularly black nations.
Zionism. Zionism is at the fundamental root of colonialism. Zionism and colonialism and imperialism are all at the root of nations across the world continuing to be plundered for their resources while not being able to have sovereignty.
Zionism and continue to continue to continue to continue to continue to continue to be under the foot of white supremacy.
And many of you all do not know this and you haven't studied it, but yet you stand on the opinion that it is irrelevant and that it does not matter.
And this is the result of a very, very concerted effort in this nation to really push ignorance.
And to push willful ignorance and to diminish the ability to have access to knowledge.
And it's annoying because I really do think people would be able to have the capacity to grow if they could get the nutrients.
Like, you know, I'm on a book tour that I call a mission vision book tour right now.
And it's been really beautiful to just see the willingness that people have who are showing up to say, I don't know and I want to know.
Who are showing up to be curious.
Who are showing up to live in their empathy.
To reconnect and to rewire, right?
To decolonize from the psychological operations that have been being performed on them and their ancestors, right?
So, you know, like I'll be in Houston tomorrow, then New Orleans, and then I'll be in Atlanta on Saturday.
We'd love to get some more RSVPs for the Atlanta book talk.
And then I'll be in Dallas.
And, you know, I want you to understand that I am not looking for, I'm not looking for you to trust me.
I'm not looking for you to, you know, build me up.
I'm simply just looking for you to listen for the curiosity of yourself.
You know, when people ask me like, well, then who are we supposed to vote for?
I'm not going to tell you who to vote for, but I'm going to tell you what's what.
I'll tell you that.
I'm going to tell you what's what.
And I'm going to tell you that all of these people that are running for office are performers.
Some more than others.
So, it just behooves you to change your perspective on what an election is.
Y'all think you're voting somebody in to, like, represent you.
And that's simply not what's going on.
So, like I have said many times before, and I will say it again, the Democrats are not your friends.
The media, the mainstream media is not either.
And if you want to be manipulated and lied to, then that is your choice.
However, I find it odd.
And I will not be a party to doing that anymore.
And that's basically what I see here.